bellashoot.com 2016-11-07

# Privacy Policy | Bellashoot

## Bellashoot Privacy Policy

**Last updated August 27, 2014**

Bellashoot LLC (“Bellashoot”, “we”, the “Company”) has created this privacy policy in to order explain our privacy practices. The following discloses our information-gathering and -dissemination practices for our Bellashoot website (the “Site”), services and the Bellashoot mobile application (collectively, the “Service”). By using the Service, you do hereby warrant and represent that 1) you have read, understand and agree to all terms and conditions stated herein, including our Terms of Use, available at http://www.bellashoot/terms, incorporated herein by reference, which govern the use of the services offered by Bellashoot, and 2) that you are giving Bellashoot permission to use and store such information consistent with this privacy policy and our Terms of Use. A user of the Service is hereinafter referred to as a “User,” or collectively, the “Users.”

### Links and Information

This website contains links to other websites. Please review Section 10 of our Terms of Use, available at: http://www.bellashoot.com/terms, for more information.

### Information Received by Bellashoot

**Personal Information.** Bellashoot collects personal information only if you voluntarily choose to share such information with Bellashoot. You may browse the Site without disclosing any personal information. However, in order for you to take advantage of particular opportunities provided through the Service, we may require that you furnish personal information. When you register your account, sign up for newsletters, complete forms for optional programs, surveys, contests and other entries, and through communications transmitted through Bellashoot, applications and your use of the Bellashoot mobile application, we may collect information including your name, email address, phone number, date of birth and gender. You also may choose to send Bellashoot personally identifying information in an email message containing information or inquiries about the Service.

**Anonymous or Aggregated Data.** Bellashoot collects and stores certain data about the use of the Service on an aggregate and/or anonymous basis. Such information may include pages viewed and search terms entered on the Site. Bellashoot does not link this information to anything personally identifiable to you.

**Cookies and Other Technologies.** When you visit websites on the Internet, your browser may automatically transmit information to the websites you visit throughout every visit. Like many websites, we may use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We may utilize persistent cookies that only Bellashoot can read and use to save your login information for future logins to the Service, to hold session information, and to track user preferences. We may utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Service, to better understand how you interact with the Site and to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Service, to track the number of entries in Bellashoot promotions, sweepstakes and contests and to identify visited areas of the Site and Service. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you log off from the Site and Service and then close your browser. Third party advertisers on the Site may also place or read cookies on your browser and we may use Flash cookies (or local shared objects) to store your preferences or display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you will not be able to use all portions or all functionalities of the Service. We and our service providers may also use "pixel tags," "web beacons," "clear GIFs," or similar means in connection with the Service and HTML-formatted email messages to, among other things, track the actions of Users and email recipients, to determine the success of marketing campaigns and to compile aggregate statistics about Site usage and response rates. We may also engage one or more third party service providers to serve online advertisements on our behalf. They may use a “pixel tag” to collect anonymous information about your visits to this Site and to other websites, and they may use that information to target advertisements for goods and services. This information is collected anonymously, in a manner that does not personally identify you.

**Logged Data.** Logged data is collected by our servers and third parties such as Google Analytics about connections, devices and network conditions while a User is connected to the Service. We collect and store certain types of system log data whenever you interact with the Service, including search terms, pages viewed, the IP address, the browser brand and version, what device is being used and the operating system of the device. We collect logged data to better understand which devices are using the Service and their performance levels in order to continually optimize our software and Services to provide the most efficient and stable service to Users.

**IP Address.** When you visit and interact with the Site, Bellashoot and/or third parties with whom Bellashoot has contracted to provide services to Bellashoot may collect your Internet Protocol Address (“IP Address”), which is a number that is automatically assigned to the computer that you are using by your Internet Service Provider. This number is identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever you visit the Site, along with the time(s) of your visit(s) and the page(s) that you visited. We use IP Addresses to monitor the regions from which Users navigate the Site and for fraud prevention purposes.

**Social Networking Services.** We may collect information about you when you register for or log into the Service by logging into an account that you have with third parties, including social networking services (“SNS”) such as Google, Facebook, or Twitter. When you sign up for the Service for the first time by using an SNS sign-in, we collect the credentials about you that you make available in your privacy settings within that SNS.

The Company also collects and uses personal data regarding its employees (“Employee Data”), which may include: name, address, job title and other job information, location, compensation information, identification number, employment history, and a copy of employment agreements.

Only authorized Bellashoot staff have access to your Personal Information in its entirety. Other staff may have access to portions of this information if it pertains to their job duties.

### Bellashoot's Use of Personal Information

Bellashoot uses Personal Information for the following general purposes:

  * to provide the Service,
  * for identification and authentication, and fraud prevention,
  * to analyze Site usage and improve the Service,
  * to contact you and deliver administrative notices and communications relevant to your use of the Service,
  * for internal market research, troubleshooting problems, and detecting and protecting against error, fraud or other criminal activity,
  * for distribution to third-party contractors that provide services to Bellashoot and partners of Bellashoot who are bound by privacy restrictions at least as restrictive as those set forth in this Policy,
  * to enforce our Terms of Use, and
  * as otherwise set forth in the Policy.

Although we ensure that our third party agents (“Agents”) receiving your information are bound by privacy restrictions at least as restrictive as those set forth in this policy, Bellashoot is not responsible for any issues that may arise regarding the Privacy Policies of any of its affiliates or advertiser. By using this website, you do hereby agree to hold Bellashoot harmless from any claims and/or damages that may arise from the actions of any of its affiliates and/or advertisers.

Two things drive Bellashoot's decisions regarding the use of information collected from Users: 1) improving user experience by offering personalized services, content and advertising, and 2) market research.

Ads are a standard part of user experience on the Internet, and Bellashoot believes that targeted advertising enhances this experience. Bellashoot may use Cookies and other Technologies and Personal Information to place ads where they believe interested parties will see them.

In addition to banner ads, Bellashoot may advertise products, companies and events that we think might interest you through the email address you provide.

Bellashoot may use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. In connection with this advertising, we, along with third-party business partners, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) to allow our third-party business partners, including Google, ad servers, and ad networks, to serve you advertisements (“ads”) based on your prior visits to our Service. These ads are delivered to you on third-party websites and services across the Internet. These third-party business partners use technology to send, directly to your browser or mobile device, the ads and ad links that appear on third-party sites, and will automatically receive your IP address when they do so. Along with cookies, they may also use other technologies (such as JavaScript, device identifiers, location data, and clear gifs, see above) to compile information about your browser’s or device’s visits and usage patterns on the Service, and to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to optimize and personalize the advertising content. Bellashoot does not sell, rent, or share the information we collect directly from you or about you from third parties with these third-party business partners for such parties’ own marketing purposes. You may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page or you may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics opt-out page. Google has additional information available about their Remarketing Privacy Guidelines, Policies, and Restrictions.

Bellashoot may analyze Personal Information and Web Navigational Data based on your interests and may use the analysis from this information in a way that doesn’t reveal a User’s personal information (“Market Research”) in order to: * Market the Service * Improve the likelihood of a sale to a group of Users * Increase the likelihood that a group's experience with the Service is relevant to its interests as a whole

Bellashoot uses data at the individual level to sell products and services to Users who express an interest in these products and services, through a poll for example, or to Users who can be presumed to have an interest based on results from our Market Research.

Bellashoot may use your cell phone number to call or text you in order to provide the Service. If you would like more information about our policy, or to opt out, please review Section 7 of our Terms of Use, available at http:www.Bellashoot/terms or email info@Bellashoot.com.

Employee Data is only used for the purposes of facilitating the performance of certain administrative tasks and functions relating to general employment and for processing and investigating reports under the Company’s codes and policies (“Employee Data Purposes”).

We use Financial Information solely as authorized by you in accordance with the Service.

### Choice/Opt-Out

You may opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners, remove your information from our database, and choose to not receive future communications unrelated to the Service, including through the preferences section of your account.

During registration you choose whether to receive correspondence from either Bellashoot or its partners and whether you want to participate in a variety of Bellashoot programs. This information remains on your Profile where you can, at any point, easily edit it to indicate that you have changed your mind. After logging on, go to your account settings and make your selections. If you purchase anything through Bellashoot, we may occasionally contact you with information about special events, sales, activities, promotions, contests, submission opportunities and programs. You always have the option to ask Bellashoot not to contact you with this information again.

If you receive unsolicited email from a Bellashoot domain, please contact us at info@bellashoot.com.

### Do Not Track

We do not track or respond to browser “Do Not Track” Requests.

### Bellashoot's information retention policy

To preserve the integrity of our databases, we may retain information submitted by Users for an indefinite length of time. If required by law, as is the case to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we will delete Personal Information by erasing it from our database. We will also respond to User requests to delete or correct account or Personal Information, which you can do by contacting Bellashoot at info@bellashoot.com, or by selecting the “Settings” option under your account icon in the top right corner of your home page or on your device.

### Bellashoot security of collected information

Your Bellashoot account is password-protected so that only you and authorized Bellashoot staff have access to your account information. You may change your password at any time. In order to maintain this protection, do not give your password to anyone. If someone who represents to you they are Bellashoot staff and asks for any personal account information, including password, check their URL. If it doesn't say they are info@bellashoot.com, they aren’t. Also, if you share a computer, you should sign out of your Bellashoot account and close the browser window before someone else logs on. This will help protect your information entered on public terminals from disclosure to third parties.

This site incorporates physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, including Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") encryption to protect your personal information online, and we also take several steps to protect your personal information in our facilities. Access to your personal information is restricted. Only employees and third parties who need access to your personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to your personal information. Finally, we rely on third-party service providers for the physical security of some of our computer hardware. We believe that their security procedures are adequate.

Bellashoot uses industry-standard procedures and safeguards designed to protect the privacy of personal information. Bellashoot employees with access to personal information are required to follow specific practices concerning its proper handling. Our vendors and their employees who may need access to user information are held to strict confidentiality requirements. At times, we may retain third parties to analyze data we collect on our website, and to administer the services provided, solely to help us provide and improve our products, services and websites. These suppliers and other third parties are not authorized by us to use your personal information in any other way. We may have to use personal information to investigate complaints and protect Bellashoot and its Users, in compliance with the law, our Terms of Use, and Bellashoot policies.

While we use industry-standard precautions to safeguard your personal information, we cannot guarantee complete security. In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your personal information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. To the extent we have your email address, we may notify you by email.

While Bellashoot will use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of all credit card and all other personal information, we expressly disclaim any liability for any unauthorized access to or use of our secure servers and/or any and all personal and/or financial information stored therein, and you agree to hold Bellashoot harmless for any damages that may result therefrom.

### With whom does Bellashoot share information?

When you submit information to Bellashoot, it is collected, processed and maintained solely by us or by third party agents who are bound by privacy restrictions at least as restrictive as those set forth in this policy. We may allow our business partners to collect information about Users that is not extremely sensitive Information. If you would like to opt out from the onward transfer of your information to our non-agent partners, you may send us an email at info@Bellashoot.com. Include the word "privacy" in the subject line of the email and all your registration information in the body of the email.

Some Bellashoot content is "sponsored by" or "presented by" other companies. Bellashoot shares market research data (how the sponsorship performed, names of contest winners, etc.) collected on this website or via email surveys with these partners. This information is aggregate and not linked to specific users.

Partners may sponsor promotions, contests and sweepstakes that require you to reveal details such as your name, address or phone number. Always check their privacy policy before revealing information about yourself. If you don't want these sponsors to have your personal information, you can choose to not participate.

Bellashoot reserves the right to disclose Personal Information from both private and public areas of this website at our discretion, if required by law or if we are given reason to believe, in our sole discretion, that someone is causing injury to or interference with the rights of Users, the general public, or Bellashoot, to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process.

Finally, Bellashoot reserves the right to transfer, sell and/or distribute all information collected through the Service to an affiliate, subsidiary, or third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or part of our business, assets or stock. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the new entity follows this Privacy Policy with respect to your Personal Information, as and to the extent required by applicable law.

### How can Users edit their information?

Bellashoot believes strongly in giving you the ability to access and edit your personal information. To update your personal info, access your account by clicking your profile picture and username at the top of any page. There you can view, update and correct your account information. You may edit your account information at any time -- all you need is your username and password.

Our databases automatically update any Personal Information you edit in your profile, or that you request we edit. Information transmitted through boards, chats, polls or through any other means remains in our databases and becomes the property of Bellashoot upon submission.

### Notification of changes

Bellashoot's security and privacy policy are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary. This policy might change as Bellashoot updates and expands the Service. Bellashoot will endeavor to notify you of these changes by email, but will not be liable for any failure to do so. Bellashoot also encourages you to review this privacy policy periodically. If you do not understand any of the terms or conditions of any of Bellashoot's policies, you may inquire regarding the same via email at info@bellashoot.com.

### Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly collect maintain or solicit any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. Please DO NOT use or access the Bellashoot Service in any manner at any time if you are less than 13 years of age. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you are a parent or guardian and discover that your child under the age of 13 has obtained a Bellashoot Service account, then you may alert Bellashoot at info@bellashoot.com and request that Bellashoot delete that child’s Personal Information from our systems.

### California Privacy Rights

Users who are California residents may request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, certain information about the personally identifiable information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personally identifiable information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to info@bellashoot.com.

### Users from outside the United States

Bellashoot and its Service are based in the U.S., and the Company’s offices are headquartered in the U.S. Please be aware that information you provide to Bellashoot that it obtains as a result of your use of the Service may be processed and transferred to the U.S. and be subject to U.S. law. The privacy and data protection laws in the U.S. may not be equivalent to such laws in your country of residence. By using the Website, participating in any of the Service, or by providing Bellashoot with your information, you consent to this collection, transfer, storage, and processing of information to and in the U.S. and other countries. Bellashoot will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### How can I reach Bellashoot staff?

If you have technical problems, questions or other issues related to your use of Bellashoot, please click the Contact link on the home at the bottom of any page of this website. You can also contact us at info@bellashoot.com.

Bellashoot's staff will respond to all requests sent through mail or email from Users and parents interested in knowing more about what personal information is stored on the Bellashoot database, or if they want their personal information nullified, or have additional questions regarding privacy.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you may contact us at info@bellashoot.com.
